<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
 <project label="Translator" visible="true">
  <description>&lt;p&gt;iDigi Dia project sample containing a custom device (translator) and a custom
  presentation (channel viewer).&lt;/p&gt;
  </description>
  <demo_requirements>
  To run this example you will need:
    * A Digi Python compatible device to host the application.
    
  This example requires the Device Manager's Connection Mode = Local Area Network/USB/Serial
  (set under the Device Manager’s General Tab).
  </demo_requirements>
  <demo_setup>
  1) Make sure the hardware is set up correctly:
       a) The Digi device is powered on.
       b) The Digi device is connected directly to the PC or to the Local 
          Area Network (LAN) by the Ethernet cable. In case the device does 
          not have Ethernet interface, make sure it is connected directly to 
          the PC by the corresponding USB or serial cable.
          
  2) If you are using a ConnectPort X3 device:
       a) Configure the iDigi Dia elements using the Smart Project Editor:
           * Set the 'Console' presentation type to 'serial'
             Type: serial
           * Remove the 'Web' presentation.
           
       b) Connect the device DB-9 serial port to the PC.
       
       c) This demo requires a serial console terminal in order to interact 
          with the application. You can use the embedded terminal included 
          with the Digi ESP for Python or any other serial terminal 
          application.
          
          Configure the terminal and open a serial connection with the Digi 
          device:
               * Baud Rate: 115200
               * Data Bits: 8
               * Stop Bits: 1
               * Parity: None
               * Flow Control: None
          
          Refer to the topic "Terminal view" of the "Digi ESP for Python" 
          documentation for more information.
  </demo_setup>
  <demo_run>
  The example is already configured, so all you need to do is to build and 
  launch the project.
  
  While the application is running the custom presentation will print out
  every 5 seconds a table with the values of the 'translator0.InputString' 
  and 'translator0.OutputString' channels.
  
  Use the iDigi Dia Console presentation to inspect and change the channel 
  values. This presentation is a Command Line Interface (CLI) for browsing 
  channels, system settings and historical logs:
     1) For ConnectPort X3 and X-Trak 3 devices, the CLI is enabled on the 
        Serial Port of the device.
        
     2) For the rest of devices, the CLI is enabled on TCP port 4146.
     
  Connecting to the CLI presentation allows us to interact with the Dia's 
  channels and settings. Once the Dia connection is established, the following 
  welcome message and prompt are presented:

  Welcome to the iDigi Device Integration Application CLI.
  =>>
 
  Type 'help' at the command prompt in order to see what commands can be 
  executed. Typing 'help' followed by the name of a command will give us 
  additional information on that command.
  
  The 'channel_set' command sets the value for the given channel: 
  
  =>> channel_set translator0.InputString "Hello"
  
  The 'channel_dump' command dumps the value of all channels:
  
  =>> channel_dump

   Device instance: translator0

   Channel                  Value              Unit     Timestamp          
   ------------------------ ------------------ -------- -------------------
   InputString              Hello                       1955-05-16 20:52:16
   OutputString             Hola                        1955-05-16 20:52:16
  
  </demo_run>
  <type>com.digi.dpdev.project.dia</type>
  <data_path>data</data_path>
  <id>dia_translator</id>
  <mainFile>dia_translator.yml</mainFile>
  <sampleFiles></sampleFiles>
  <sourceFolder></sourceFolder>
  <icon></icon>
  <platforms>
    <platform>ConnectPort X2</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X2B</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X2D</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X2e ZB</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X2e Wi-Fi ZB</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X2 SE</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X3</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X4</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X4 H</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X4 IA</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X4 NEMA</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X4 4G</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X5</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X5 F ZB GPRS</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X5 F ZB Wifi GPRS</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X5 R ZB GPRS</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X5 R ZB Wifi GPRS</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X5 R ZB Wifi CDMA</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X5 R Wifi GPRS Iridium</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort X8</platform>
    <platform>Embedded Gateway</platform>
    <platform>ConnectCore 3G 9P 9215</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort WAN Wi</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort WAN VPN</platform>
    <platform>ConnectPort WAN GPS</platform>
    <platform>Connect WAN 3G IA</platform>
    <platform>Digi Connect SP Python</platform>
    <platform>Digi Connect Wi-SP Python</platform>
  </platforms>
  <tested_on>
  ConnectPort X4
  ConnectPort X3
  </tested_on>
</project>
