<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
 <project label="ConnectPort X3 Getting Started" visible="true">
  <description>&lt;p&gt;iDigi Dia project sample designed for the ConnectPort X3 Family.&lt;/p&gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;This project shows an example of an iDigi Dia framework containing two virtual 
  devices. One of them increments a counter channel every second, and the other, 
  multiplies it by 2.&lt;/p&gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;The iDigi DB presentation reads the value of both channels and sends a file 
  with this information to iDigi every 10 seconds. The files are named 
  'couter_samples0.xml -> couter_samples9.xml' (and overwritten as needed) so no more 
  than 10 files are stored on iDigi.&lt;/p&gt;
  
  &lt;p&gt;The RCI presentation allows a remote access to the channels information.&lt;/p&gt;
  </description>
  <demo_requirements>
  To run this example you will need:
    * A ConnectPort X3 device to host the application.
    * An iDigi account.
    
  This example requires the Device Manager's Connection Mode = Local Area Network/USB/Serial 
  (set under the Device Manager’s General Tab).
  </demo_requirements>
  <demo_setup>
  1) Make sure the hardware is set up correctly:
       a) The Digi device is powered on.
       b) The Digi device is connected directly to the PC by the corresponding 
          USB or serial cable.
  2) Make sure the device is added to your iDigi inventory.
  </demo_setup>
  <demo_run>
  The example is already configured, so all you need to do is to build and 
  launch the project.
  
  While the application is running, the value of the 'counter' channel 
  ('template_device.counter') will be incremented every second. The value 
  of 'count_by_two' channel ('transform_device.count_by_two') will be also 
  recalculated multiplying the 'counter' value by 2.
  
  The Digi device will send to the iDigi server the value of both channels 
  every 10 seconds.
  
  To verify that the xml files are being uploaded to iDigi successfully, 
  follow these steps:
     1) Press the "iDigiME" button of the toolbar to access to your iDigi 
       account.
    2) Once there, go to the "Storage" section from the left menu.
    3) Open the storage folder corresponding with your Device ID.
    4) You should be able to see a folder called "x3_counter". Open it and 
       verify it contains the xml files sent by the application. They should 
       have the following name:
           couter_samples[n].txt - Where [n] is the index of the file.
    5) You can open any of the files to see the channel values they contain.
  </demo_run>
  <type>com.digi.dpdev.project.dia</type>
  <data_path>data</data_path>
  <id>x3_getting_started</id>
  <mainFile>x3_getting_started.yml</mainFile>
  <sampleFiles></sampleFiles>
  <sourceFolder></sourceFolder>
  <icon></icon>
  <platforms>
    <platform>ConnectPort X3</platform>
  </platforms>
  <tested_on>
  ConnectPort X3
  </tested_on>
</project>
